Register of the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary Sound Recordings, 1967-1980
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program list of Viewpoint and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary, 1975-1979
  - Items, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Investigative Agencies, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Drugs, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - SALT, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pushers, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Kearney, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alaska, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Good News, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Youth and Crime, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Enterprise, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Aid to Vietnam, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Individual, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taxation, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Energy, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Restitution, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Freedom, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - An Angry Man I, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - An Angry Man II, Program 77-22, 8 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Superintendent's Dilemma, Program 77-22, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Capitalism/Socialism, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Socialism, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Inflation and the Property Tax I, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Inflation and the Property Tax II, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Public Employees, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Red Hen, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - President Coolidge, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Education, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Christmas 1977, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bread Machine and Janeway, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Incredible Bread Machine, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - People Power, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Button, Button, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - America's Strength, Program 77-23, 21 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Snail Darters, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nicaragua I, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nicaragua II, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Visas, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Security, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Health Insurance I, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Health Insurance II, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Social Security, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Martin Luther King, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Coffee, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Automobiles, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - NEA, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Kidco, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Apples, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Herman Kahn, Futurist, Program 77-24, 29 November 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt II, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Christmas, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - American Farm School I, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - American Farm School II, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Human Rights I, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Human Rights II, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Human Rights III, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taxes, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Our Country, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Healthy Competition, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: John McClaury
  - Pot, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Social Security, Program 78-01, 9 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Big Mo, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Panama, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - St. Stephen's Crown, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Korea, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Independents vs IRS, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Regulation, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare Reform, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Looking Out a Window, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Jobs, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pity the Middle Class, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Father and Son, Program 78-02, 27 January 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Panama Canal Debate, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Spaceships, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Redwoods, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Swordfish, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Farm Day, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Limitation 1978 Style, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Steel, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Labor, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Economy, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Neighborhoods, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cuba, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Treaties, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Neutron Bomb, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bakke, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Blind on the Left, Program 78-03, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Canal, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Treaties, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt Talks I, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt Talks II, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cubans and Russians, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt II, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Two Worlds [Foreign Aid, World Bank], Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - War {Panama], Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Suicide Lobby [MFS, anti-communist conspiracy], Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Budget, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mineral King, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Local Control I, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Local Control II, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Gift [Indian headdress], Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Items, Program 78-04, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Canal, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Time, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - China, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bill Simon, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Missing Person, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Three Martini Lunch, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government [Renegotiation], Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Spies, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - No Pay, No Vote, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - B-1 Bomber, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Farm, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Regulators, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - General James, Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Desk-Cleaning [Foreign Policy], Program 78-05, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Guinea, Program 78-06, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Life and Death [7 yr old Eduardo, Leukemia], Program 78-06, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Christmas, Program 78-06, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Do Right, Program 78-06, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - School Days, Program 78-06, 20 February 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government Security, Program 78-06, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Sports, Program 78-06, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Fighting Cal Graham, Program 78-06, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Greensville County Elections, Program 78-06, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Snails and Signboards, Program 78-06, 13 March 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nit Picking, Program 78-06, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Communications I, Program 78-06, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Communications II, Program 78-06, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Soviet Consumer, Program 78-06, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Air Cargo Deregulation, Program 78-06, 3 April 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Japan I, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Japan II, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Japan III, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taiwan I, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hong Kong, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Women, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Education, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alger Hiss, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rhodesia, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Pacific, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Seal Hunt, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Dulles Airport, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Castro's Prisons, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Health Care, Program 78-07, 15 May 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taxes Again, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Security, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hearst, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Spending, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Energy, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Oil, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Russia, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Planes, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Drugs, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Foolishness, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Money, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - New Talk from a Labor Leader, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salaries, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Davis-Bacon Act, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Education, Program 78-08, 5 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - U.S. - China Relations, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Normalization, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - District of Columbia, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Fraud, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - SALT Talks, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cities, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Stamps, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Asia, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Asia II, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Press, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alex. Solzhenitsyn, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alex. Solzhenitsyn II, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Inflation, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Malibu, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-09, 27 June 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mirages, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Lumber, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Freedom of Speech in Russia, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Stanley Yankus, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Charity, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - School Busing, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Wedding, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - South Africa, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cuba, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Castro, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Walter Knott, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Trains, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Chiefs of Staff, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Proposition 13, Program 78-10, 15 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt Talks I, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Salt Talks II, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Employment, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Economics I, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Economics II, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Paperwork, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Religious Freedom, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rome, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - South Seas, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Prisoner Exchange, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Local Government Center, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Alternative Energy and Uncle Sam, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Refugee Success Story, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Accidents, Program 78-11, 31 July 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Income Tax, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - British Health Care, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - History, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Brainwashing I, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Brainwashing II, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Revolt, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Left and Right, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Average Man, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Polls and Guns, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Guantanamo, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government Cost, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pay Raise, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous [Prop. 13], Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Two Worlds, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Technology, Program 78-12, 7 August 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mexico's Oil, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Olympics, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Prop. 13 Fallout, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Terrorism, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Land, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pot, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Needed: Better Use of National Forests, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mail, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Africa, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Utilities, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bugs, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government Payroll, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Free Enterprise, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-13, 19 September 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - District of Columbia, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Amtrak, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Bi-Lingual, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Federal Lands, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Ocean Mining, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow I, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow II, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow III, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow IV, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow V, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rostow VI, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - End of [an] Emergency, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Argentina, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Environment, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Soviet Nuclear Power, Program 78-14, 10 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Letelier I, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Letelier II, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Intelligence and the Media, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Escalator, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power I, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power II, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Waste, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Carrier, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pensions, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Self-help in the Neighborhoods, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Chinese Libertarians, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Davis-Bacon Act, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-15, 31 October 1978 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Private Schools, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Toys, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Hope for Cities, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Basketball, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Horse and Rider I, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Horse and Rider II, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - China, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Salt II, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Jokes, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - An Accurate Thermometer, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Wood I, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Wood II, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Bilingualism, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Taxation, Program 78-16, 28 November 1978 (Box 8)
  - Christmas Day, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Salt II, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Panama Canal, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Gambling on the Dollar, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - The Checkoff Ripoff, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Gas, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Taxes, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Keep of the Grass, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Helsinki Pact [Easy Germany], Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Bread, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Business Tax, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - ERA, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous I, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Textbooks, Program 78-17, 12 December 1978 (Box 8)
  - Taiwan, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taiwan I, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taiwan II, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taiwan III, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Jim Hendricks, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Patent Medicine I, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Patent Medicine II, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Human Rights, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Health Insurance, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Telescope I, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Telescope II, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous I, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous III, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - South Africa, Program 79-01, 1 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Phone, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - OPEC, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Federal Trade Commission, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Official Rules, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Anti-Poverty Abuses I, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Anti-Poverty Abuses II, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Wind Energy in Denmark, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Counterintelligence, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Australia I, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Australia II, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Peace Corps, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Policeman, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous 1, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: John McClary
  - Miscellaneous 2, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Regulations, Program 79-02, 19 January 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Proposition 13 and the Post Commission I, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Proposition 13 and the Post Commission II, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Deregulation, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Dishonest Environmentalists, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Fish, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Constitutional Amendment, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pot, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Saying "No" [Part] I, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Saying "No" [Part] II, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Conspiracy, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Lawrence Welk, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Income Tax, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hamburgers, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Long Walk, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-03, 13 February 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nancy, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Lettuce Strike, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Taiwan's Future, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - POW, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cuba, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The 100 Club, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - CIA, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Inflation, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Human Rights, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Comparisons, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power II, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power I, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Higher Standard of Living, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Student Economists, Program 79-04, 6 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Panama, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Small Business I, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Small Business II, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Scared Straight, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Palestine, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rhodesia, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - District of Columbia, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rural Renaissance, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Washington Weather, Program 79-05, 27 March 1979 (Box 8, Box 2)